Okay, next section is breast cancer.
This is the longest section and particularly the highest yield section in this chapter,
so we're going to spend a little bit more time doing this section than we have on the prior sections.
Before we begin, let's remind ourselves that the breast cancer is the most common carcinoma in women by incidence,
and of course we're excluding skin, so the most common carcinoma in women by incidence excluding skin,
and it's the second most common cause of cancer mortality, the first most common cause being lung cancer.
The risk factors are mostly related to estrogen exposure, and when you look at this list that I placed here in your text,
you'll see that that becomes very quickly evident.
So for example, female gender is the first risk factor. That's the number one risk factor.
When you think about breast cancer, for every 100 cases, 99 will occur in a female, and only one will occur in a male,
and of course that has to do with estrogen. Age is a risk factor.
Generally speaking, the classic patient who has breast cancer is a postmenopausal female,
and you can see breast cancer in younger patients, but it begins to suggest that there may be a genetic abnormality
that's driving that breast cancer, but classically speaking, just you really think about breast cancer
as a disease of postmenopausal females. Early menarche and late menopause would be a sign of increased exposure to estrogen,
and if the breast sees increased exposure to estrogen, there's going to be an increased risk for breast cancer.
Obesity, remember that adipose tissue has the ability to convert androgen to estrone, which is a type of estrogen,
and that would therefore increase the risk for breast cancer.
Atypical hyperplasia, this refers to a patient having a prior biopsy in which atypical hyperplasia was seen.
Remember that when we talked about atypical hyperplasia in the prior section,
we mentioned that when patients have atypical hyperplasia on a biopsy, that increases their risk five times relative to the normal population
of developing invasive breast cancer in either breast, and that's what we mean by atypical hyperplasia here.
And of course, if there's atypical hyperplasia, it kind of implies that there must be excess estrogen on board
or some sort of estrogen-related risk factor because that's why the hyperplasia is occurring.
It's driven by estrogen often.
And then finally, one of the risk factors is family history, in particular, first-degree relative with breast cancer.
And it's important to note here who the first-degree relatives are.
So they include sister, mother, and daughter.
Sister, mother, daughter.
Those are the three first-degree relatives.
Now, the first of the cancers that we're going to talk about is ductal carcinoma in situ.
I think it's best to just take a step back and establish a few basic principles before we actually go into the subtypes of cancer.
So let's do this.
Let's go back and remind ourselves that the functional unit of the breast is something called the terminal duct lobular unit.
So here would represent the terminal duct, and then you're aware that the lobule contains these glands
and that these glands are really the milk-producing glands of the breast.
Now, it's possible when you have cancer that you can get a malignant proliferation of cells within the duct.
And when you get a malignant proliferation of cells within the duct, that's called ductal carcinoma in situ.
And the key feature here is that these malignant cells are bound by this basement membrane.
So that's ductal carcinoma in situ.
If these ductal carcinoma in situ cells walk up the duct and eventually come out to the skin of the nipple,
into the epidermis of the nipple, then that's called Paget's disease of the nipple.
So when you have Paget's disease of the nipple, that is a ductal carcinoma in situ that has walked its way up the duct.
So that's important to note.
If these malignant cells invade through the basement membrane and into the surrounding stroma,
then we call that invasive ductal carcinoma.
So that's another subtype of breast cancer.
It's also possible to have a malignant proliferation of cells within the lobule.
That would be called lobular carcinoma in situ.
And if these malignant cells invade through the basement membrane and into the connective tissue,
then we would call that invasive lobular carcinoma.
So these are really our four main subtypes of breast cancer.
Ductal carcinoma in situ, invasive ductal carcinoma, and then lobular carcinoma in situ, and invasive lobular carcinoma.
And what we're going to do over the next few slides is now provide some more detail of this paradigm.
So this is the global theme that you have to have in your mind as you walk through breast cancer.
Let's go back and begin our discussion with ductal carcinoma in situ.
So as I said, ductal carcinoma in situ is a malignant proliferation of cells in the ducts.
There is no invasion of the basement membrane.
Now, because these cells are simply growing in ducts, you wouldn't normally be able to detect it as a mass.
It usually doesn't produce a mass.
Instead, it's going to be detected as calcification on mammography.
And the idea here is that if you've got this duct, and I'm showing you this duct head-on,
and let's say it's loaded with these malignant cancer cells,
there is no blood supply in the duct, within the duct itself.
Remember, the blood supply is out here.
And so these cells, as they grow, especially if they're high-grade and rapidly growing cells,
the center will often die.
And when the center dies, you've got dead cells.
And remember that it's possible to get calcification on top of dead cells,
which is called dystrophic calcification.
So you can develop dystrophic calcification on top of these dead cells,
and mammogram can then pick up that calcification.
Now, remember that calcifications are not always malignant.
For example, we talked about two other lesions in this chapter
in which we could see calcifications, but they were not malignant.
They were benign.
So can you recall those?
Number one, fat necrosis.
Remember that I said that when a patient gets fat necrosis,
they get saponification of that fat, and it can be calcified.
And number two, in the discussion of fibrocystic changes,
is I talked about one change called sclerosing adenosis
and told you that that is often calcified as well.
And so therefore, that could be detected as calcification on mammogram.
So this is something important to bear in mind.
Now, there are actually multiple different patterns of ductal carcinoma in situ.
However, the one that's super high yield and most important for board exams
and probably for your level of training is the one to be aware of.
It's called the comedotype.
In the comedotype, you have high-grade cells with necrosis
and dystrophic calcification in the center of the ducts
is exactly what I've already drawn.
Here's a picture of that.
This is a duct cut head-on.
So here you've got this duct.
And you can see that this duct is loaded with all these cells.
So there's too many cells.
And then in the center, there's this necrosis.
And the center of that necrosis is calcified.
So this is the classic example of the comedotype of ductal carcinoma in situ.
Now, remember, I told you that if you have DCIS,
for example, in this duct, and then it climbs up its way through the duct
and eventually gets into the skin of the nipple in particular,
we call that Paget's disease of the nipple or Paget's disease of the breast.
So this is ductal carcinoma in situ that extends up the ducts to the skin of the nipple.
It's going to present with nipple ulceration and erythema.
And, of course, if you see a patient and they've got Paget's disease of the nipple,
let's say that you have a patient and they've got this nipple ulceration and erythema,
and you do a biopsy and you prove that there's Paget's disease of the nipple,
that would tell you that there must be a cancer within the breast.
And that's a very important point because if you go back to your gynecologic lectures,
remember that there is also a disorder called extra mammary Paget's disease
where you get malignant cells within the epidermis of the vulva.
And in that particular disorder, there was no underlying carcinoma.
So we do have to make a big deal here about the fact that in Paget's disease,
there will be a cancer someplace in the breast.
So that's important to know.
Here's what Paget's disease of the nipple looks like.
Obviously, you can see this area of ulceration and disturbance of the epithelium
or the epidermis of the nipple.
Here's what it would look like on biopsy.
You normally have your squamous cells, and then in between the squamous cells,
you've got all of these cells with this kind of lighter-colored cytoplasm,
and these are the malignant cells walking their way up the skin or the epidermis of the patient's nipple.
And so, again, this is Paget's disease of the nipple.
Invasive ductal carcinoma is when you actually have the malignant cells go through the basement membrane
and now invade into the connective tissue.
And it classically forms duct-like structures so that when you look at the tumor,
you'll actually see these round duct-like structures.
Now, this is the most common type of invasive carcinoma.
It presents as a mass, and that mass can be detected by physical exam or mammography.
Physical exam will usually detect a mass that's about two centimeters or greater,
whereas mammography can pick up a mass at about one centimeter or greater.
And so mammography is a very good test because it allows us to detect breast cancer at a much earlier stage.
One of the important things to recognize concerning breast cancer is that as the tumor begins to spread through the breast,
it can result in dimpling of the skin or retraction of the nipple.
Now, let's remember that retraction of the nipple is not always due to cancer.
It can be due to inflammatory conditions as well.
However, in this particular case, it is a consequence of cancer, so just something to be aware of.
Now, when you're worried about cancer in the breast, if you have a mass and you're particularly worried,
you're going to do a biopsy.
And when you have invasive ductal carcinoma, you're going to see duct-like structures in a desmoplastic stroma.
And what we mean by desmoplastic stroma is that you have connective tissue growing with the tumor,
and that connective tissue is there to support the tumor and provide its structural support, stromal support, we could say.
And that's called desmoplastic stroma.
Now, there are some special subtypes of invasive ductal carcinoma to be familiar with.
The most common circumstance is that you have your everyday invasive ductal carcinoma.
But there are four subtypes.
They're all high yield, and I want to talk about each of these individually.
So the first is called tubular carcinoma.
And the important thing about tubular carcinoma is that the cancer produces tubules,
little round circular spaces.
And the little round circular spaces look very much like normal breasts.
Sometimes it's difficult to distinguish this from normal.
And there's a few features that will help you to determine that this is actually malignant.
Number one, you'll see a desmoplastic stroma.
So you can clearly see here that there's all this kind of blue-gray connective tissue in between,
and that is the desmoplastic stroma.
And number two, if I were to test these cells to see if there was a second cell type,
the second cell type would be absent.
Let's go back and remind ourselves that the normal ducts and lobules of the breast,
they normally have two cell types.
They have an epithelial cell, and then underneath that, they have a myoepithelial cell.
However, when you look at cancer, cancer would not have two cell types.
It's not normal.
So you would only see one cell type here.
And so if I didn't see a second cell type,
that would also prove to me that I'm dealing with a tubular carcinoma.
Now, one important thing about tubular carcinoma is that it has a very good prognosis.
It has a particularly good prognosis.
The second type of special invasive ductal carcinoma is called mucinous carcinoma.
A key feature is that you have malignant cells floating in pools of mucus.
And so you can see these are the malignant cells.
These are not normal.
And look at all of the mucus back here that they're floating in.
So the presence of malignant cells in mucus is called mucinous carcinoma.
There are two important things to know about this subtype.
Number one, it has an excellent prognosis, just as tubular carcinoma has an excellent prognosis.
Perhaps one way to think about it would be that the tumor cells are all stuck in mucus,
so they can't go anywhere.
Now, number two, this usually occurs in elderly women.
So it's seen in, and so it's particularly seen in elderly women.
The third subtype of, special subtype of breast cancer that I want to talk about
is called inflammatory carcinoma.
Now, when a patient has inflammatory carcinoma, they present with a breast that's highly erythematous
and swollen.
So it looks like the patient has acute mastitis.
However, you put the patient on antibiotics, or perhaps the patient may not be feeding,
but let's say the patient is feeding.
You put the patient on antibiotics, and it doesn't really resolve.
Now you become more concerned that perhaps it's not an infection, but it could be,
for example, something called inflammatory carcinoma.
So then you do a biopsy, and when you do a biopsy, you find the characteristic feature,
which is that this type of tumor is characterized by the presence of cancer within the dermal
lymphatics, as I've circled here.
When you have cancer in the dermal lymphatics, the cancer blocks the dermal lymphatics and
decreases the drainage of the breast.
That then results in a swollen erythematous breast, and this is called inflammatory carcinoma
of the breast.
Now, a couple important things about this type of cancer.
Now, number one, one very high-yield point to be aware of is the fact that it is a clinical
pathologic entity.
You need to see inflammatory changes in the breast clinically, and then you must prove that there
is tumor in dermal lymphatics pathologically.
So both of these pieces are essential for this diagnosis.
That's the first point.
The second point is that you should be aware that this has a very poor prognosis, and I
think that's easy to understand because the tumor is already sitting in the dermal lymphatic
spaces and now has access to the lymph nodes and potentially the rest of the body.
And the third point that I want to make about this tumor is to remember to always have it
in the back of your mind when you see a patient that you think has acute mastitis.
So especially on an examination, they can tell you that there's a woman and she's feeding,
and you kind of make a diagnosis of acute mastitis, but that after the antibiotics, the disease
process does not resolve.
And that you need to be careful.
Whenever you have acute mastitis, you need to make sure that you're not dealing with an
inflammatory carcinoma.
So for example, if you have a woman with acute mastitis and you give antibiotics, it's important
to see that woman five or ten days later to ensure that the antibiotics took care of the
problem and that you didn't miss, for example, an inflammatory carcinoma of the breast.
Again, this has a very poor prognosis.
The fourth special subtype, which I don't have a picture of, but it is in your text and
it is high yield, it's called medullary carcinoma.
The special thing about medullary carcinoma is that you have high grade malignant tumor
cells with a bunch of inflammatory cells in the background, particularly lymphocytes
and plasma cells.
Now what's important about this subtype is that there's an increased propensity for this
subtype in patients with BRCA1 mutations, and that's high yield.
So again, in medullary carcinoma, in which you have high grade malignant cells in an inflammatory
background, there's an increased propensity for that subtype of cancer to arise in patients
with BRCA1 mutations, and again, that is high yield.
Now, after we've completed the ductal types of cancers, we then go to the lobular types
of cancers, and let's remind ourselves that I said that if this is the terminal duct and
this is the lobular unit, and you've got all of these little globule, all of these little
glands within the lobule, if you get a malignant proliferation of cells within the lobule, then
we call that lobular carcinoma in situ.
And if you get a malignant proliferation of cells that invades, then we call that invasive
lobular carcinoma.
LCIS, or lobular carcinoma in situ, is a malignant proliferation of cells in the lobules.
Of course, there is no invasion of the basement membrane.
What's interesting about this entity is that it's usually detected incidentally.
What that means is that you find it by accident.
It doesn't produce a mass.
It doesn't produce calcifications.
So you biopsy the breast for one reason.
Let's say there is a mass or a calcification that you're worried about, and then it so happens
that by chance, or incidentally, you discover that the patient has lobular carcinoma in situ.
Now, one of the key features about lobular carcinoma in situ is that when you look at the cells,
let's pretend that this is the terminal duct and this is the lobular unit, and you've got
these glands here, when you look at the cells, the cells are often discohesive, which means
they are not stuck to one another.
Instead, they're very separate from one another.
And that's important because one of the key characteristics of this particular tumor is
that it lacks an adhesion molecule called ecadherin.
Now, ecadherin is the glue that allows cells to stick together.
It's a cellular adhesion molecule.
It's glue that allows these cells to stick to one another.
So, if lobular carcinoma in situ is lacking ecadherin, it wouldn't be hard to understand
why the cells often appear discohesive or not attached to one another.
This is particularly high yield concerning lobular carcinoma, that it lacks ecadherin due
to a mutation in that gene.
Now, often, lobular carcinoma in situ is actually multifocal and bilateral, so that if a patient
has lobular carcinoma, for example, here in the breast, it'll also be here and here
often, and it would not be uncommon to also find it in the other breast in various locations.
So, lobular carcinoma in situ is often multifocal and bilateral.
Now, a current understanding of lobular carcinoma in situ is that it is a risk factor for the
future development of breast cancer.
So, we don't try to excise lobular carcinoma in situ.
Instead, we use pharmacologic agents such as tamoxifen, which is an anti-estrogen agent,
with the hopes of decreasing the risk of those cells actually progressing to eventually become
invasive carcinoma.
And then, in addition, we would give close follow-up.
So, our current understanding of lobular carcinoma in situ is that it's more of a risk factor
than it is a quote-unquote malignant proliferation.
So, generally speaking, with lobular carcinoma in situ, there's a low risk of progression
to invasive carcinoma.
Invasive lobular carcinoma is a tumor of lobular cells that invades beyond the basement membrane
into the actual connective tissue of the breast.
Now, one of the interesting things is that, remember, in ductal carcinoma in situ, the
cells produce ductal-like structures.
However, in invasive lobular carcinoma, the cells classically invade in a single-file pattern.
The cells are all dispersed and single from one another.
The reason why this occurs is because the tumor cells lack E-cadherin.
Remember that E-cadherin is a cellular adhesion molecule that allows cells to stick together.
So, that would then allow those cells to make ducts.
However, in the case of invasive lobular carcinoma, there is no E-cadherin.
Therefore, the cells invade singly, quote-unquote, in a classical single-file pattern.
And that's super high yield.
Super high yield to know why.
E-cadherin mutations.
Here's a classic picture, and you can see that there's these tumor cells, which are invading
singly in a single-file pattern, and not really producing ductal structures.
Now, generally speaking, when we have a patient that has breast cancer, the next thing the
patient's going to want to know is, what's my chance of survival?
Remember that the main way by which we determine prognosis is the TNM staging system.
Now, the T, again, stands for tumor, and that's based on the size of the tumor.
The N stands for metastasis to local lymph nodes, and so we would assess the axillary
lymph nodes to determine the N stage.
And then the M refers to distant metastasis.
Now, metastasis is the most important prognostic factor.
If a patient has metastasis outside of the region, outside of the breast and the axillary lymph
nodes, that would be a very poor prognostic sign.
Although metastasis is the most important factor, however, most patients don't usually
present with metastasis.
So, therefore, the most useful factor becomes spread to axillary lymph nodes.
And I hope that's clear, because that's particularly high yield.
I'm going to repeat it one more time.
Metastasis is most important.
However, because most patients don't present with metastasis, what becomes particularly useful
in those patients is the second most important factor, which is spread to the axillary lymph
nodes.
The way by which we determine spread to the axillary lymph nodes is called the sentinel
lymph node biopsy.
So, let me just highlight the principle here.
Basically, if a patient has a tumor within the breast, let's say that this is a cancer within
the breast, our understanding is that that breast would then drain to the axillary lymph
nodes, and that we would like to examine the axillary lymph nodes to determine whether
there's cancer in those nodes, because it affects whether we should, for example, give
the patient chemotherapy or not.
Now, when we have this cancer within the breast, and we'd like to assess the axilla, one way
to do it would be to remove all of the axillary lymph nodes.
However, the problem with that is that if the patient has no cancer in the lymph nodes,
then we've removed the lymph nodes, and now the patient has no draining from the
arm, and therefore would develop swelling of the arm as a complication.
It's an acceptable complication if the patient has cancer, but the reality is that 75% of
patients who have breast cancer don't even have cancer in the lymph nodes, and so in 75%
of our patients, we were causing arm swelling when we didn't really need to.
So, someone came up with a brilliant idea called the sentinel lymph node biopsy, where the notion
is that you inject the breast with either a blue dye or a radioactive substance, and allow
that blue dye or radioactive substance to go to the lymph nodes.
Now, it so happens that the lymph nodes in the breast are organized in tiers, so that you
kind of have a line of lymph nodes, and then another line of lymph nodes, and another line
of lymph nodes behind that.
So, the goal in the sentinel lymph node biopsy would be to inject dye or radioactive agent,
and then allow that dye to assess the very first line of lymph nodes that is being drained
by the breast.
Once you've marked those lymph nodes with the blue dye or the radio tracer, you open up
the axilla, and you remove those lymph nodes.
If those lymph nodes are negative, you can make the assumption that the rest of the lymph
nodes behind those nodes are also negative, whereas if these lymph nodes are positive,
you'll go back and remove, at that point in time, all of the other lymph nodes.
So, that's called the sentinel lymph node biopsy, and it allows us to take minimal number of
lymph nodes while still accurately staging the patient.
So, that's a good paradigm to be aware of when thinking about prognosis in breast cancer.
Now, we can also determine some predictive factors when dealing with breast cancer.
And predictive factors predict response to treatment.
That's the purpose of determining predictive factors.
And there are three key predictive factors that we need to be aware of.
The first is ER, the second is PR, and the third is HER2 new gene amplification.
Now, basically, the notion is that if the tumor cells express estrogen receptor and the tumor
cells express progesterone receptor, then that would mean that we could potentially expect
a response when we gave them anti-estrogenic agents, like tamoxifen.
And so, we will take a patient's tumor cells and test whether they express estrogen receptor
and progesterone receptor.
And these are two very important tests we do to predict response to anti-estrogenic agents,
such as tamoxifen.
And so, this would be two of the important tests.
The third is amplification of the HER2 new gene.
Now, remember that the HER2 new, I'm going to remind you, going back to our neoplasia lecture,
HER2 new is a cell surface growth factor receptor.
And if the patient has excess HER2 new, classically due to gene amplification,
that's important, it's due to gene amplification,
that excess receptor can result in excess growth of the cell,
which can then drive the proliferation of the tumor.
And so, this is an important predictive factor because we have antibodies that we've designed
called HERceptin or trastuzumab.
Now, we have antibodies against those receptors,
and patients who have excess receptor can be treated with this antibody.
Here's a couple stains that I've provided to show you how we actually do this.
So, when we have a breast cancer, we can do immunohistochemical stains for estrogen receptor,
as I'm showing here.
And, of course, the estrogen receptor complex is present in the nucleus.
Now, remember that the receptor itself is present in the cytoplasm,
but when it binds its partner, it then moves to the nucleus.
And so, you can clearly see that the nuclei of all these cells are brown,
indicating that the tumor is positive for estrogen receptor.
Now, progesterone receptor would look exactly the same
because it is also a receptor that translocates itself to the nucleus.
HER2 new, on the other hand, would not be present in the nucleus,
but is present on the surface of the cells on the cytoplasm.
And I've already explained that HER2 new is a growth factor receptor
that would be seen on the surface of the cells.
Now, a slide, which is that HER2 new is a cell surface receptor.
Remember that it's a proto-oncogene that, when amplified, becomes an oncogene.
Now, when you think about all of these three key predictive factors,
that can create a wide variety of possibilities.
For example, if you're thinking about ER and then PR and then HER2 new,
it's possible that some patients could have ER positive, PR positive, HER2 negative tumors.
It's also possible that you could be ER positive, PR negative, HER2 negative.
It's possible to be negative for ER, negative for PR, and positive for HER2, etc., etc.
But there's one particular subtype to be aware of,
and that's when patients are negative, negative, negative,
negative for all three predictive markers.
And in those cases, patients are called triple negative.
What's important about this subtype is that it has a poor prognosis,
and that also African-American women have an increased propensity
to develop triple negative carcinoma.
Hereditary breast cancer represents 10% of cases of breast cancer,
and there are some features that you can see within a patient
that would suggest hereditary breast cancer.
For example, if the patient has multiple first-degree relatives with breast cancer,
you might think about the fact that the patient may have hereditary breast cancer.
If the patient has tumor at a premenopausal age,
remember that breast cancer is classically a disease of postmenopausal females.
However, if the patient gets cancer at a premenopausal age,
you might think about testing the patient for hereditary breast cancer.
And also, if a patient develops multiple tumors, that would be highly unlikely,
and so again, we would test for hereditary breast cancer.
When considering hereditary breast cancer,
BRCA1 and BRCA2 are currently the two most important single-gene mutations
in the domain of hereditary breast cancer.
Let's remind ourselves that BRCA1 patients have an increased risk
for both breast and ovarian carcinoma,
and I'd like to remind you of a couple high-yield points here.
Number one, breast cancer, there's an increased propensity
for medullary carcinoma of the breast.
Remember that discussion that we just had a few moments ago.
Now, medullary carcinoma is not the most common type of breast cancer
in these particular individuals.
However, there is an increased propensity compared to the normal population.
And then the second is to remind you that when you consider the ovarian carcinoma
in the BRCA1 patients, it's classically a serous carcinoma,
and I'd like to very clearly remind you
that it doesn't only increase the risk for ovarian carcinoma,
but this can also arise within the fallopian tube,
and that's a high-yield principle that I talked about in your gynae lectures.
When you think about BRCA2, it's classically associated with breast cancer in males.
That's one of the classic associations with BRCA2.
Now, I'd like to remind you, when patients have a hereditary breast cancer,
they may elect to undergo prophylactic mastectomy.
So, for example, if a woman learns that she's got a BRCA1 or BRCA2 mutation,
she may choose to actually have both breasts removed.
If both breasts are removed, however,
it's very important to note that a small risk still remains
for the development of breast cancer,
and that's because sometimes we have excess breast tissue
that can go, for example, into the muscle
or may be present up in the axilla, etc.
And so, although prophylactic mastectomy sharply would reduce the risk
of future development of cancer, the risk does not become zero,
and those patients still need to be watched carefully.
Male breast cancer is the last discussion that we want to have,
and all I'd like to say about this is, number one, it's rare.
Remember that for every 100 cases of breast cancer, only one will involve a male,
whereas 99 will be seen in a female.
It presents as a subareolar mast.
That's to be expected because we know that the vast majority of breast tissue
is in the subareolar region in a male,
whereas, again, the vast majority of breast tissue in a female
is in the upper outer quadrant.
So, usually it's going to be in an older male,
and it can produce nipple discharge,
and the reason it produces nipple discharge
is because the tumor is developing right underneath the nipple.
Now, most often, patients who have male breast cancer
will develop a ductal carcinoma,
and the idea here goes back to embryology,
and that is that when you've got a male breast,
you do develop terminal ducts,
but you don't yet develop those lobules.
And so, most of the breast tissue in males is actually ducts
with very few lobules,
and so they usually develop invasive ductal carcinoma.
And the last point is that there's an association with BRCA2 mutation,
as I just stated a moment ago,
and there's also an increased risk in patients with Klinefelter syndrome.
So, this concludes our discussion of breast cancer,
and now we can move on to the next chapter.